Guide to the Lisa Jaronski Zine Collection, 1992-2005 RL.11009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Lisa Jaronski zine collection
1992-2005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
Jaronski, Lisa
RL.11009
5.4 Linear Feet 9 boxes
A collection of about 470 zines, mostly of the personal nature, mostly written by women, acquired during the period of the late 1990s to early 2000s.
Biographical Note
Lisa Jaronski, aka, Lazy Jane, is from upstate New York. She is the author of the zines When Swinging Next to You, and Jurm, as well as a few single-issue zines.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Collection Overview
Collection consists of zines primarily from the U.S., with a small number from Canada, Australia, and New Zealand. Many of the zines were acquired through trade and larger organized swaps referred to as “Lazy Jane’s Zine Trades” arranged by the collector (ie: send in 30 copies of your zine, get 30 unique zines back from the other participants).
Arrangement
The collection is divided into two series: Zines by Women and Zines by Men, each of which is organized alphabetically by zine title.
Provenance
The Lisa Jaronski Zine Collection was acquired by the Rubenstein Library as a gift in 2013.
Fanzines; Fan magazines -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Underground press publications -- United States; Women -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Self-publishing -- United States; Zines -- United States; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture; Jaronski, Lisa
- Zines by Women
  - 20 Bus, 9 Issues: 1-3, 5-10. Sept. 93- May 01. San Francisco, CA (Box 1)
  - 25 days, 1 Issue: 1. 1999. Wien, Austria; Los Angeles, CA (Box 1)
  - 422, 1 Issue: 1. 1999. Sydney, Australia. (Box 1)
  - 575, 1 Issue: 1. Amherst, MA (Box 1)
  - Aberration, 4 Issues: 10-13. Dec. 96, Apr. 97, Jul.98, Winter 00/01. Milwaukee, WI (Box 1)
  - A Bowl of Oatmeal, 2 Issues: 7-8. San Francisco, CA (Box 1)
  - Additive Free, 1 Issue: 1. Feb. 98. Norwell, MA. (Box 1)
  - A DIY Crafts Primer, 1 Issue: 1. (Box 1)
  - A Girl and Her Bike, 1 Issue: 6. Nov. 99. Winnipeg, MB Canada (Box 1)
  - Alabama Grrrl, 5 Issues: 3, 5-8. Jun. 98, Winter 99, Jul. 99, Dec. 99. Pittsburgh, PA; Auburn, AL; Lawrence, KS. (Box 1)
  - A Liar's Book of Stars, 1 Issue: 8. Summer 98. Olympia, WA (Box 1)
  - Anomaly, 1 Issue: 1. Ballston Spa, NY (Box 1)
  - A Peculiar Twirling Skirt, 1 Issue: 1. Spring 99. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 1)
  - Aperture, 1 Issue: 1. Feb 00. Pownal, ME (Box 1)
  - Arg, 1 Issue: 1 (Box 1)
  - A Renegade's Handbook to Love & Sabotage, 3 Issues: 1-2, 5. Apr. 00, Sept. 00, Mar. 02. Portland, OR (Box 1)
  - Arrowed, 7 Issues: 2-3, 6-10. Ann Arbor, MI (Box 1)
  - Backyard, 1 Issue: 1 (Box 1)
  - Bathtub, 1 Issue: 4. Montreal, QC Canada (Box 1)
  - Beyond, 2 Issues: 1-2. Autumn 99, May 00. Hannover, Germany (Box 1)
  - Billy's Mitten, 1 Issue: 10. Summer 97. Tucson, AZ (Box 1)
  - Birthdays & Christmas//Faking Distance, 1 Issue(Split Issue): 1. Sept. 04. Portland, OR (Box 1)
  - Bitch Dyke Whore, 1 Issue: 6. Olympia, WA (Box 1)
  - Blender Children, 1 Issue: 5. Summer 00. Topeka, KS (Box 1)
  - Blue Skies, 2 Issues: 1-2. Sept. 00, Nov. 00. Portland, ME (Box 1)
  - Buttons, Assorted zine-related buttons (Box 1)
  - Cacofonia Deliciosa, 1 Issue: 3. Watertown, MA (Box 2)
  - Candles for Girls, 1 Issue: 5. Madison, WI (Box 2)
  - Can't Stop the World, 2 Issues: 1-2. Autumn 99, Spring 00. Amherst, MA (Box 2)
  - Carryout, 1 Issue: 3. Summer 98. Santa Cruz, CA (Box 2)
  - Cataclysm Girl, 1 Issue: 6. Chicopee, MA (Box 2)
  - Charlie's Ants, 1 Issue: 1. Ontario, CA (Box 2)
  - Cherry Cherry Red, 1 Issue: 6. June 00. Portland, OR (Box 2)
  - Christine Bactine, 1 Issue: 1. Sept. 99. St Albans, WV (Box 2)
  - Citronella, 1 Issue: 1. July 00. Allston, MA (Box 2)
  - Clean Yer Room, 2 Issues: 3-4. Spring 98, Fall 98. Seattle, WA (Box 2)
  - Consider Yourself Kissed, 3 Issues: 2-4. Summer 99, Feb. 00. Lenexa, KS (Box 2)
  - Continental Drift, 1 Issue: 4. Rockford, IL (Box 2)
  - Cory, 1 Issue: 1. Sept. 99. Malta, NY (Box 2)
  - Couldn't Kill Her If You Tried, 2 Issues: 1-2. Dec 97, Feb 98. Carle Place, NY (Box 2)
  - Counterclockwise, 1 Issue: 3. Feb. 00 (Box 2)
  - Creamsicle, 3 Issues: 1-3. Gettysburg, PA (Box 2)
  - Crème-filled, 1 Issue: 5. 2001. Milwaukee, WI (Box 2)
  - Crude Noise, 1 Issue: 4. July 04. Pipersville, PA (Box 2)
  - Daffodil, 5 Issues: 15-18, 20. May 98, Sept. 98, Jan. 99, Nov. 99, Dec. 02. Willington, CT (Box 2)
  - Dangeresque, 1 Issue: 1. Apr. 04 (Box 2)
  - Daydream Faerie, 3 Issues: 2, 4-5. Laguna Nigel, CA (Box 2)
  - Dear Boy, 1 Issue: 1. Oct. 99. Avon Lake, OH (Box 2)
  - Dear Mr. Bush, 2 Issues: 1-2. Jul 02, Feb 03. Roxbury, MA (Box 2)
  - Dear Prudence, 1 Issue: 1. May 00. Drain, OR (Box 2)
  - Deliciosa, 1 Issue: 4. Watertown, MA (Box 2)
  - Dilemma, 1 Issue: 4. Fall 04. Toronto, ON Canada (Box 2)
  - Divinity, 1 Issue: 1. Jan 99. Evansville, IN (Box 2)
  - Don't Stop (Stop), 2 Issues: 1, 5. Spring 00, Summer 02. Amherst, MA; Japan (Box 2)
  - Doris, 1 Issue: 9. Asheville, NC (Box 2)
  - Drivel, 2 Issues: 2, 5. Overland Park, KS (Box 2)
  - Drop Kick Kitten, 1 Issue: 2. Southbury, CT (Box 2)
  - Faerie Dust, 1 Issue: 1. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 3)
  - Fancy, 8 Issues: 7-13, 14. Feb 98, Apr 98,Summer 98, Winter 98-99, Jul 99, Jun 00. Boston, MA (Box 3)
  - Few Are Born Beautiful, 1 Issue: 1. Boston, MA (Box 3)
  - For the Girl who Couldn't Choose Between the Shower or the Bath, 1 Issue: 1. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 3)
  - For the Love of Gardening, 1 Issue: 1. Oct 97. York, England (Box 3)
  - Fragile, 1 Issue: 1. Jan 00. Minneapolis, MN (Box 3)
  - Freewheeler/Polarity, 1 Issue (Split Issue): 11/16. Dec 97. Tucson, AZ; Jamestown, CA (Box 3)
  - Fuzzy Heads are Better, 1 Issue: 6. Jan 98. Toronto, ON Canada (Box 3)
  - Galaxy Distribution, 3 Issues: 1-3. Feb 98, Jan 99. Mendon, MA (Box 3)
  - Girl in a Box (Box 3)
  - Girl Swirl, 1 Issue: 11. Feb 04. Pennsylvania, PA (Box 3)
  - Glosspot, 1 Issue: 1. 1998. Portland, OR (Box 3)
  - Guh, 1 Issue: 1 (Box 3)
  - Happy Pancakes, 1 Issue: 1. Jan 00. Queensland, Australia (Box 3)
  - Heartburning, 1 Issue: 1. Nov 99. East Hartford, CT (Box 3)
  - Her Red Self, 1 Issue: 2. Winter 00. East Hartford, CT (Box 3)
  - Honestly! Katie John!, 1 Issue: 8 (Box 3)
  - Hope, 1 Issue: 17. Sept 00. Portland, OR (Box 3)
  - Horror Vacui, 1 Issue: 1. Montreal, QC (Box 3)
  - I am a Camera, 2 Issues. Strawberry Hills, NSW Australia (Box 3)
  - I Draw Stars, 1 Issue: 1. 1999. Arroye Grande, CA (Box 3)
  - I Dreamed I Was Assertive, 1 Issue: 3. Spring 00. Tampa, FL (Box 3)
  - If You Were Here We Would Be Best Friends, 1 Issue: 1. March 00. Boston, MA; Montreal, QC (Box 3)
  - I'm Not Waiting, 1 Issue: 2. Parsippany, NY (Box 3)
  - Inbetween, 1 Issue: 1. 2002. Boston, MA (Box 3)
  - Indulgence, 3 Issues: 4-5 and 9. Summer 99, Summer 00, Spring 04. Pownal, ME (Box 3)
  - In Moving Clouds, 5 Issues: 11-15. Mar 99, Aug 99, Jan 00, Jul 00. Ottawa, ON Canada (Box 3)
  - Inside the Test, 1 Issue: 1. Northampton, PA (Box 4)
  - Into the Unknown, 1 Issue: 1. Winter 99. Portland, OR (Box 4)
  - Invincible Summer, 1 Issue: 1. March 01. Portland, OR (Box 4)
  - Is There Any Room For Freewill?, 1 Issue: 1 (Box 4)
  - Java Turtle, 1 Issue: 'Best of' Issue. Santa Barbara, CA (Box 4)
  - Journal of an Insomniac, 1 Issue: 1. Gettysburg, PA (Box 4)
  - Journalsong, 1 Issue: 5. Portland, OR (Box 4)
  - Jurm: The Ideas and Teachings of Caitlinism, 3 Issues: 1-3. 1998. Malta, NY (Box 4)
  - Kickstand, 2 Issues: 9-10. Spring 98, Nov 98. Santa Cruz, CA (Box 4)
  - Kiss Off Fanzine, 1 Issue: 8. Nov 02. Ottawa, ON Canada (Box 4)
  - Laburnum/Mister Fujiyama Loves You, 1 Issue(Split Issue): 3 1/2 and 4 1/2. Spring 04. Upper Black Eddy, PA (Box 4)
  - Lamb's Lettuce, 1 Issue: 1. Greeley, CO (Box 4)
  - Laughter and the Sound of Tecups, 2 Issues. Mar 00, May 00. Strawberry Hills, NSW (Box 4)
  - Lazy Eye, 1 Issue: 1. Jun 99. Gahanna, OH (Box 4)
  - Leather, 1 Issue: 1. Waukesha, WI (Box 4)
  - Life Sucks, 7 Issues: 1-5, 2 not numbered. 1999, 2000. Auckland, New Zealand (Box 4)
  - Lipstick My Espionage, 1 Issue: 2. New York, NY (Box 4)
  - Looks Yellow, Tastes Red, 7 Issues: 16, 18-22, 26. Jul 98, Jan 00, Jan 01. Wellfleet, MA (Box 4)
  - Losing My Religion, 1 Issue: 4. Fall 00. Atlanta, GA (Box 4)
  - Love Letter, 1 Issue: 1. Jan 00. St Albans, WV (Box 4)
  - Love & Science, 1 Issue: 1 (Box 4)
  - Lucky Lucky, 1 Issue: 1. Gahanna, OH (Box 4)
  - Lust and Lunacy, 1 Issue: 1. May 99. San Jose, CA (Box 4)
  - Make Me Numb, 1 Issue: 14:Vols. I, II. Nov 03. Pensacola, FL; Brattleboro, VT (Box 4)
  - Mango, 1 Issue: 1. 2000. Auckland, New Zealand (Box 4)
  - Matilda, 1 Issue: 3. Spring 04. Ottawa, ON Canada (Box 4)
  - May, 1 issue: 1 (Box 4)
  - Me, 1 Issue: 1. Dec 98. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 4)
  - Melt the Snow, 9 Issues: 4-12. Weston, ON (Box 4)
  - Memorytown USA, 4 Issues: 3-6. Winter 99, Summer 99, Sept 00, Oct 01. Middletown, CT (Box 4)
  - Merge Disorder, 1 Issue: 3. Jan 00. Somerset, NJ (Box 5)
  - Metamorphosis: A Small Piece of Semi-Fiction, 1 Issue: 1. Mar 00. St James, NY (Box 5)
  - Moon Lagoon, 1 Issue: 1. Jan 99. Joensuu, Finland (Box 5)
  - Moons in June, 2 Issues: 1-2. Jun 98, Feb 99. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 5)
  - Muffin Bones, 1 Issue: 17. Summer 97. Stamford, CT (Box 5)
  - My Life as a Liar, 1 Issue: 1. Geronimo, CA and Amherst, MA (Box 5)
  - My Own Personal Star, 1 Issue: 1 (Box 5)
  - Needles and Pins, 2 Issues: 1-2. Autumn 99, Winter 00. Dickson City, PA (Box 5)
  - Neon Zoe, 1 Issue: 2. Dec 00. New York, NY (Box 5)
  - New Year, 1 Issue: 2. Jun 00. Seattle, WA (Box 5)
  - No Outlet, 1 Issue: 1. May 00. Glen Cove, NY (Box 5)
  - Nothing, 5 Issues: 5-9. Mar 96, Apr 96, Jun 96, Aug 96, Feb 97. Willimantic, CT (Box 5)
  - Not Quite Israfel, 4 Issues: 5-8. Summer 99, Oct 99, Jun 00, Jul 01. Bloomington, IN (Box 5)
  - Oh January, 1 Issue: 3. Spring 04. Meadville, PA (Box 5)
  - Oppress This, 7 Issues: 4-7, 9-11. Apr 98, Summer 98, Nov 98, Winter 98, Jul 99, Nov 99, Spring 00. Avon Lake, OH (Box 5)
  - Other Ramona, 2 Issues: 1-2. 99/00. Kingston, ON Canada (Box 5)
  - Our Star Boxed Rollerskates, 1 Issue: 1. Allston, MA (Box 5)
  - Out of Order, 9 Issues: 1-4, 6-10. Spring 99, May 99, Jun 99, Jul 99, Aug 99, Sept 99, Dec 99, Feb 00, Jun 00. Cedar Falls, IA (Box 5)
  - Pander Zine Distro, 2 Issues. Spring/Summer 99, Fall/Winter 98-99. Minneapolis, MN (Box 6)
  - Pantophobia: The Fear of Everything, 1 issue (Box 6)
  - Parfait, 2 Issues: 1-2. 03, 04-05. Brooklyn, NY (Box 6)
  - Pelvic Control, 1 Issue: 7. Jan 98. New York, NY (Box 6)
  - Picaflor, 1 Issue: 1. 1999. Tampa, FL (Box 6)
  - Pink Tea, 5 Issues: 2-6. May 98, Jan 99, Spring 99, Summer 99, Winter 00. Boston, MA (Box 6)
  - Please Seat Yourself, 1 Issue: 1. Mar 99. Cambridge, MA (Box 6)
  - Pocket, 1 Issue: 9. Ambridge, PA (Box 6)
  - Popular Delusion, 1 Issue: 5. Tulsa, OK (Box 6)
  - Power Candy (Box 6)
  - Project 16, 1 Issue: 3. (Box 6)
  - Promise On Everything, 4 Issues: 4-7. Aug 99, Apr 00, Oct 00. Mendon, MA (Box 6)
  - Pumpkin (Box 6)
  - Queen of the Kangaroos, 1 Issue: 1. Blue Island, IL (Box 6)
  - Rags to Riches, 1 Issue: 1. 1999/2000. Wodonga, Victoria Australia (Box 6)
  - Raw Sugar, 1 Issue: 1. Dec 99. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 6)
  - Red Hooded Sweatshirt, 6 Issues: 1-6. 98, May 99, Winter 99, Spring 01, 02, Spring 03. Boston, MA (Box 6)
  - Rejection, 1 Issue: 4. Bradenton, FL (Box 6)
  - Replica, 3 Issues: 2, 7-8. N. Ridgeville, OH (Box 6)
  - R Is Part of Trouble, 1 issue (Box 6)
  - Riot Grrrl Press, 1 Issue. Apr 99. Washington D.C. (Box 6)
  - Rock Star With Words, 1 Issue: 4. Jun 02. (Box 6)
  - Root, 3 Issues: 1-3. Halifax, NS Canada (Box 6)
  - Rugburn Spectacular, 1 Issue: 1. Mount Vernon, NY (Box 6)
  - Satellite Whispers, 1 Issue: 1. Atlanta, GA (Box 7)
  - Selected Writing, 1 Issue: 1. May 99 (Box 7)
  - Shake Bottle Shake, 2 Issues: 1-2. Irvine, CA (Box 7)
  - Short Fiction, 1 Issue: 1. 1999. Olympia, WA (Box 7)
  - Slideshow, 1 Issue: 1. Boston, MA (Box 7)
  - Snailmania, 5 Issues: 1-3, 5-6. Chesterfield, MO (Box 7)
  - Sock Monkey Social Life, 1 Issue: 6. Jan 04. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 7)
  - Some Misplaced Joan of Arc, 1 Issue: 3. May 99. Los Angeles, CA (Box 7)
  - Someone Loves Me in Ohio, 1 Issue: 5. Jamaica Plain, MA (Box 7)
  - Some Things Are Impossible, 1 Issue: 1. Oct 03. (Box 7)
  - Sparrow, 1 Issue: 1. 2004. (Box 7)
  - Spiral Girl, 1 Issue: 1. (Box 7)
  - Square Suckers, 1 Issue: 8. Apr 98. Johnson City, TN (Box 7)
  - Stargirl, 1 Issue: 1. Ontario, CA (Box 7)
  - Stick Figure Zine Distribution, 1 Issue. Summer 98. Atlanta, GA (Box 7)
  - Stimuli, 1 Issue: 1. Ballston Spa, NY (Box 7)
  - Strawberry Moon, 1 Issue: 1. Macungie, PA (Box 7)
  - Struggle, 1 Issue: 1. Assonet, MA (Box 7)
  - Subject to Change, 5 Issues: 5-8, 11. Summer 99, Winter 99, Winter 00, Summer 00, Winter 02. N Cambridge, MA (Box 7)
  - Suburbia/Tennis and Violins, 1 Issue (Split Issue): 8/2. Point Richmond, CA; Tampa, FL (Box 7)
  - Suburban Gothic, 1 Issue: 5. Jul 04. Bellevue, NE (Box 7)
  - Supreme Nothing, 6 Issues: 2, 6-10. Burton, OH (Box 7)
  - Tangent, 1 Issue: 1. Auckland, New Zealand (Box 7)
  - Texttrap, 3 Issues. Winter 00, Winter 02. Gahanna, OH (Box 7)
  - Textwrap, 2 Issues. Gahanna, OH (Box 7)
  - That Girl, 11 Issues: 1-11. San Francisco, CA (Box 8)
  - The 28 Day Grace Kelly Diet, 1 issue (Box 8)
  - The Bakery, 1 Issue. Sept 97. Santa Cruz, CA (Box 8)
  - The Bunny Story, 1 Issue. 1998. Windsor, ON Canada (Box 8)
  - The Charm of a Lopsided Star, 1 Issue: 1. Bloomington, IN (Box 8)
  - The Day of Wrath, 1 Issue. Amherst, MA (Box 8)
  - The East Village Inky, 1 Issue. Jan 04. Brooklyn, NY (Box 8)
  - The Fog of Clarity, 1 Issue: Vol 3. Oct 03. Mountain View, CA (Box 8)
  - The Gallery, 1 Issue. N. Ridgeville, OH (Box 8)
  - The Insatiable Cunt, 1 Issue: 3. 2003. (Box 8)
  - The Irony Tree, I issue (Box 8)
  - The Man Who Lived Inside His Camera, 1 Issue. Ottowa, ON Canada (Box 8)
  - The Messy Eater, 1 Issue. Ottowa, ON Canada (Box 8)
  - The Promise, 1 Issue. Ontario, CA (Box 8)
  - The Razor's Edge, 1 issue (Box 8)
  - The Reminders (Box 8)
  - The Rice Paper House Under My Skin, 1 Issue. Jul 00. Evansville, IN (Box 8)
  - The Science, 2 Issues: 18, 21. Aug 00, Spring 04. Sonora, CA (Box 8)
  - The Second Part, 4 Issues: 1-4. Early 02, Summer 02, Oct 03, Oct 04. Toronto, ON Canada (Box 8)
  - The Shortest Distance Between Two Points, 1 Issue: 1. Jan 04. Brooklyn, NY (Box 8)
  - The Speak Easy, 2 Issues: 1-2. N. Ridgeville, OH (Box 8)
  - The Visitors, 1 Issue. Ontario, CA (Box 8)
  - The Zinester's Etiquette Zine, 1 Issue. Long Beach, CA (Box 8)
  - This Anatomy Is Music, 1 Issue: 1. Leominster, MA (Box 8)
  - To Avoid Suffocation, 2 Issues: 5-6. Lynn, MA (Box 9)
  - Treefort, 3 Issues: 10-12. Ottawa, ON Canada (Box 9)
  - Trials of a Thinking Being, 1 Issue: 1. Portland, ME (Box 9)
  - Try, Try Again, 1 Issue. Sept 01. Halifax, NS Canada (Box 9)
  - Two Forty A.M., 1 Issue. Sept 01. Halifax, NS Canada (Box 9)
  - Underpants, 1 Issue: 2. 2000. Auckland, New Zealand (Box 9)
  - Understated, 1 Issue. Aug 99. Walla Walla, WA (Box 9)
  - Under the Stars, 2 Issues: 2-3. Nov 98, Jun 99. Caledon East, ON Canada (Box 9)
  - Valokuva, 1 Issue. Bloomington, IN (Box 9)
  - Vena Cava, 1 Issue: 4. Fall 02. Juneau, AK (Box 9)
  - Vortex, 1 Issue: 2. Remuera, Auckland, New Zealand (Box 9)
  - Warm Front Today, 1 Issue: 1. Sept 99. Weston, ON Canada (Box 9)
  - Wasabi Star, 1 Issue: 1. Mar 01. Auckland, New Zealand (Box 9)
  - Wasted Style, 1 Issue: 10. Winter 00. Boston, MA (Box 9)
  - Welcome to Alaska, 1 Issue. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 9)
  - We Should Be Whispering All The Time, 1 Issue. Laguna Niguel, CA (Box 9)
  - West of Venus, 2 Issues: 1-2. Feb 96, June 96. Tucson, AZ (Box 9)
  - When I Die, 1 Issue. Bloomington, IN (Box 9)
  - When Swinging Next to You, 6 Issues: 1-6. Malta, NY (Box 9)
  - Who Needs Boys When There's Lisa Around?, 1 issue (Box 9)
  - Wicked Violet, 2 Issues: 3-4. Wilmington, NC (Box 9)
  - Word, 6 Issues: 1-6. Feb 99, Apr 99, Aug 99, Feb 00, Nov 00, May 01. Montreal, PQ Canada (Box 9)
  - Words That Soak Up Life, 1 Issue: 1. 2001. Chicago, IL (Box 9)
  - You Might As Well Live/Hope, 1 Issue (Split Issue): 7/14. Feb 98. Annandale, NY (Box 9)
- Zines by Men
  - Always Fresh, 1 Issue: 1. Graham, NC (Box 1)
  - Apollo Astro, 6 Issues: 3-8. 2000, May 01, Summer 02, 2003, Spet 03. Ipswich, MA; Providence, RI (Box 1)
  - A Softer World, 1 issue (Box 1)
  - Atrophy Zine, 1 Issue: 5. New Rochelle, NY (Box 1)
  - Breakdown, 2 Issues: 3-4. Sacramento, CA (Box 1)
  - Breathing Iced-Tea Mix, 1 Issue: 6. Aug 99. Ambler, PA (Box 1)
  - Broken Pencil, 1 Issue: 26. Toronto, ON Canada (Box 1)
  - Caduceus Symbol, 1 Issue. Ottawa, ON Canada (Box 1)
  - Cheap Porn and Bad Food, 1 Issue: 1. Nov 98. Sacramento, CA (Box 1)
  - Cheerio Wisdom, 1 Issue: 1. (Box 1)
  - Chickfactor, 3 Issues: 10-12. Winter 97, Spring 98, Jul 99. New York, NY (Box 1)
  - Chicks Dig Scars, 1 Issue: 6. Spokane, WA (Box 1)
  - Chokehold, 4 Issues: 1-3, 5. Sacramento, CA (Box 1)
  - Clever Birds, 1 Issue: 1. Halifax, NS Canada (Box 1)
  - Dang!, 1 Issue: 1. 2002. (Box 1)
  - Delphoid Celta, 1 Issue. Allston, MA (Box 1)
  - Dishwasher, 1 Issue: 15. Portland, OR (Box 1)
  - Drop Out, 3 Issues: 4-6. Sacramento, CA (Box 1)
  - Eraser Carvers Quarterly, 1 Issue: 39. Summer 99. Clay, NY (Box 1)
  - Filling Spaces with Heat, 1 Issue: 1. 2002. Buffalo, NY (Box 1)
  - Fine Print, 1 Issue: 1. 1998. (Box 1)
  - Fish with Legs, 1 Issue: 4. Brockton, MA (Box 1)
  - Flowers from the Rain, 1 Issue: 1. Arcata, CA (Box 2)
  - French Archaeology, 3 Issues: 1-3. Aug 99, Oct 99, Feb 00. Ottawa, ON Canada (Box 2)
  - Gree, Marie!, 1 Issue: 1. 2004. (Box 2)
  - Geistenbourg Welcomes You, 1 Issue: 1. (Box 2)
  - Heartattack, 1 Issue: 18. (Box 2)
  - Horizontal Stripes, 1 Issue. Danbury, CT (Box 2)
  - Hospital for Broken Hearts/Vivian, 1 Issue (Split Issue): 1/1. (Box 2)
  - I Am Normal, 1 Issue. 2003. (Box 2)
  - Identity, 1 Issue. Baton Rouge, LA (Box 2)
  - I'm Johnny and I Don't Give a Fuck, 1 Issue: 5. Vancouver, BC Canada (Box 2)
  - Infiltration, 1 Issue: 21. Aug 03. Toronto, ON Canada (Box 2)
  - Kyle Bravo's Punk Rock Guide to Saving Money, Fighting Capitalism, & Having Fun While You're At It, 1 Issue: 1. Baton Rouge, LA (Box 2)
  - Microblast, 2 Issues: 16, 16.5. 2000. North Andover, MA (Box 2)
  - Mogwai, 2 Issues: 7-8. San Jose, CA (Box 2)
  - Moped Minis, 9 Issues. 1997-2001. Boston, MA (Box 2)
  - Mossad, 1 Issue. Franklin, TN (Box 2)
  - My Moon or More, 2 Issues: 4-5. Appleton, WI (Box 2)
  - Negative Abstract, 1 issue (Box 2)
  - Nor-i, 1 Issue: 4. Spring 99. Los Angeles, CA (Box 2)
  - Okay Eat Shit and Die, 1 Issue. 2003. Montreal, QC Canada (Box 2)
  - Otaku, 2 Issues: 4-5. Winter 99, Fall 99. Nepean, ON Canada (Box 2)
  - Punk Rock Girl, 1 Issue. Baton Rouge, LA (Box 2)
  - Rev. Richard J. Mackin's Book of Letters, 1 Issue: 12. Allston, MA (Box 2)
  - Screams From Inside, 1 Issue: 7. Philadelphia, PA (Box 2)
  - Stay As You Are, 1 Issue: 8. 2002. N. Vancouver, BC Canada (Box 2)
  - Techno, 1 Issue. Rockford, IL (Box 3)
  - The Acts of the Sinful Nature are Obvious, 1 Issue. Baton Rouge, LA (Box 3)
  - The Duplex Planet, 1 Issue: 151. 1998. Jamaica Plain, MA (Box 3)
  - The Managerial Guide to Beating Workers Into Submission, 1 Issue. Baton Rouge, LA (Box 3)
  - The Oxford Murder, 1 Issue: 1. 2004. (Box 3)
  - The Perfect Mix Tape Segue, 1 Issue: 2. 2003. Portland, OR (Box 3)
  - The Real Life Diary of a Boy, 2 Issues: 7, 9. Mar 98, Jan 99. Wilmington, NC (Box 3)
  - The Real Life Letters of a Boy, 1 Issue: 8. 1999. Wilmington, NC (Box 3)
  - Untitled, 6 issues (Box 3)
  - Y2K & Indie Rock, 1 Issue: 14. Spring 99. Chicago, IL (Box 3)
  - Yellow Edenwald Field, 1 Issue(2 Copies): 1. Winter 06-07. Buffalo, NY (Box 3)